{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which game did &quot;Sonic The Hedgehog&quot; make his first appearance in?","correct_answer":"Rad Mobile","incorrect_answers":["Sonic The Hedgehog","Super Mario 64","Mega Man"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which popular First Person Shooter (FPS) franchise, got a Real Time Strategy (RTS) game developed based on its universe?","correct_answer":"Halo","incorrect_answers":["Battlefield","Call of Duty","Borderlands"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which company did Gabe Newell work at before founding Valve Corporation?","correct_answer":"Microsoft","incorrect_answers":["Apple","Google","Yahoo"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"The most graphically violent game to precede the creation of the ESRB (Entertainment Software Rating Board) was...","correct_answer":"Mortal Kombat","incorrect_answers":["Duke Nukem","Resident Evil","Doom"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What is Pikachu&#039;s National Pok&eacute;Dex Number?","correct_answer":"#025","incorrect_answers":["#001","#031","#109"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In &quot;Super Mario 64&quot;, collecting 100 coins on a level will give you a 1-UP.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What is the main ship used by Commander Shepard in the Mass Effect Franchise called?","correct_answer":"Normandy","incorrect_answers":["Osiris","Infinity","Endeavour"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which of these is NOT a main playable character in &quot;Grand Theft Auto V&quot;?","correct_answer":"Lamar","incorrect_answers":["Trevor","Michael","Franklin"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Faust is a playable character in &quot;Guilty Gear Xrd Revelator&quot;.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Pok&eacute;mon Go is a location-based augmented reality game developed and published by which company?","correct_answer":"Niantic","incorrect_answers":["Rovio","Zynga","Supercell"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In Grand Theft Auto V, what was Michael De Santa&#039;s former surname?","correct_answer":"Townley","incorrect_answers":["De Santos","Watson","Simpson"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"&quot;Half-Life 2&quot; runs on the Source Engine.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"How many Chaos Emeralds are there in the &quot;Sonic the Hedgehog&quot; universe?","correct_answer":"7","incorrect_answers":["6","8","14"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"When was the game &#039;Portal 2&#039; released?","correct_answer":"2011","incorrect_answers":["2014","2009","2007"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In most FPS video games such as Counter-Strike, shooting which part of the body does the highest damage?","correct_answer":"Head","incorrect_answers":["Arm","Leg","Chest"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the game Dark Souls, what is the name of the region you&#039;re in for the majority of the game?","correct_answer":"Lordran","incorrect_answers":["Drangleic","Oolacile","Catarina"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the first game of the Sly Cooper franchise, what family heirloom did Sly Cooper want to steal back?","correct_answer":"Thievius Raccoonus","incorrect_answers":["Raccoon Training 101","The Art of Sneak","Raccoonus Teachus"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Who is the founder of Team Fortress 2&#039;s fictional company &quot;Mann Co&quot;?","correct_answer":"Zepheniah Mann","incorrect_answers":["Cave Johnson","Wallace Breem","Saxton Hale"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In &quot;Super Mario 3D World&quot;, the Double Cherry power-up originated from a developer accidentally making two characters controllable.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which of these characters is the mascot of the video game company SEGA?","correct_answer":"Sonic the Hedgehog","incorrect_answers":["Dynamite Headdy","Alex Kidd","Opa-Opa"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The 2005 video game &quot;Call of Duty 2: Big Red One&quot; is not available on PC.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In Team Fortress 2, being disguised as a scout or medic results in a speed boost.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which of these is NOT a Humongous Entertainment game franchise?","correct_answer":"Commander Keen","incorrect_answers":["Pajama Sam","Putt-Putt","Freddi Fish"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The main playable character of the 2015 RPG &quot;Undertale&quot; is a monster.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What is the default alias that Princess Garnet goes by in Final Fantasy IX?","correct_answer":"Dagger","incorrect_answers":["Dirk","Garnet","Quina"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In Splatoon, the Squid Sisters are named Tako and Yaki.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What video game sparked controversy because of its hidden &quot;Hot Coffee&quot; minigame?","correct_answer":"Grand Theft Auto: San Andreas","incorrect_answers":["Grand Theft Auto: Vice City","Hitman: Blood Money","Cooking Mama"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In Danganronpa: Trigger Happy Havoc, what is the protagonist&#039;s name?","correct_answer":"Makoto Naegi","incorrect_answers":["Hajime Hinata","Nagito Komaeda","Komaru Naegi"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the game &quot;Subnautica&quot;, a &quot;Spadefish&quot; will attack you.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which of the following Elite Four members from the 6th Generation of Pok&eacute;mon was a member of Team Flare?","correct_answer":"Malva","incorrect_answers":["Siebold","Wikstrom","Drasna"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In Terraria, you can craft the Cell Phone pre-hardmode.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In &quot;Mario &amp; Sonic at the Olympic Games&quot;, characters are split into how many types?","correct_answer":"4","incorrect_answers":["6","5","3"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In Pok&eacute;mon, Arbok evolves into Seviper.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"&quot;The Potato Sack&quot; was a collection of indie games released on Steam in 2011 as a promotion for which game?","correct_answer":"Portal 2","incorrect_answers":["Left 4 Dead 2","Half-Life 3","Dota 2"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which &quot;Fallout: New Vegas&quot; quest is NOT named after a real-life song?","correct_answer":"They Went That-a-Way","incorrect_answers":["Come Fly With Me","Ain&#039;t That a Kick in the Head","Ring-a-Ding Ding"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What household item make the characters of &quot;Steins; Gate&quot; travel through time?","correct_answer":"Microwave","incorrect_answers":["Computer","Refrigerator","Televison"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which &quot;Call Of Duty: Zombies&quot; map introduced the &quot;Staffs Of The Ancients&quot;?","correct_answer":"Origins","incorrect_answers":["Shangri-La","Revelations","Nuketown"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Who created the &quot;Metal Gear&quot; Series?","correct_answer":"Hideo Kojima","incorrect_answers":["Hiroshi Yamauchi","Shigeru Miyamoto","Gunpei Yokoi"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the Super Smash Bros. series, which character was the first one to return to the series after being absent from a previous game?","correct_answer":"Dr. Mario","incorrect_answers":["Mewtwo","Lucas","Roy"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Lanky, Funky, and Chunky are all characters featured in which series owned by Nintendo?","correct_answer":"Donkey Kong","incorrect_answers":["Mario","Kirby","Zelda"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the Halo series, which era of SPARTAN is Master Chief? ","correct_answer":"SPARTAN-II","incorrect_answers":["SPARTAN-I","SPARTAN-III","SPARTAN-IV"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In Counter-Strike: Global Offensive, what&#039;s the rarity of discontinued skins called?","correct_answer":"Contraband","incorrect_answers":["Discontinued","Diminshed","Limited"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which of the following weapons in &quot;Counter-Strike: Global Offensive&quot; does not have a right-click function?","correct_answer":"XM1014","incorrect_answers":["SG553","R8 Revolver","USP-S"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which member of the Velvet Room is not a playable character in Persona 4 Arena Ultimax?","correct_answer":"Theodore","incorrect_answers":["Elizabeth","Margaret","Marie"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the game &quot;Fire Emblem: Shadow Dragon&quot;, what is the central protagonist&#039;s name?","correct_answer":"Marth","incorrect_answers":["Roy","Eliwood","Robin"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which Grand Theft Auto (GTA) games have the same setting?","correct_answer":"GTA V and GTA San Andreas","incorrect_answers":["GTA V and GTA Vice City","GTA IV and GTA San Andreas","GTA IV and GTA Vice City"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which of 2 Valve Games are set in the same universe?","correct_answer":"Half-life and Portal","incorrect_answers":["Portal and Left 4 Dead","Half-life and Left 4 Dead","Half-life and Counter Strike"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the survival horror game, &quot;Cry of Fear,&quot; what was the name of Simon&#039;s close friend\/potential love interest?","correct_answer":"Sophie","incorrect_answers":["Olivia","Jessica","Alice"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What was the name of the canceled projected by Blizzard Entertainment that would be later become Overwatch?","correct_answer":"Titan","incorrect_answers":["Omnic","Omega","Ghost"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the video game &quot;Postal 2&quot;, what is the name of Postal Dude&#039;s dog?","correct_answer":"Champ","incorrect_answers":["Snoopy","Krotchy","Duke"]}]}